A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Calendars 1971-1974 (Box 1360, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Christmas (Box 1360, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Clippings (Box 1361, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Contributions (Box 1361, Folder 3-6, Box 1362, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - LSR/MFR Matching gifts, 1960-1973 (Box 1362, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Debut - Laura, Marion, Lucy (Box 1363, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Dinners/Luncheons (Box 1362, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Dinner/Luncheons - King Olav V of Norway (Box 1362, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Estate (Box 1363, Folder 2)
    Restricted - Open in 2029.
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Fallout shelters (Box 1363, Folder 3-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Finances (Box 1364, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Financial Consultants (Box 1364, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Capital Fund Reports, 1963-1971 (Box 1365, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Capital Fund - Statements (Box 1365, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Cudd & Co. (Box 1365, Folder 3-4, Box 1366, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Furnishings (Box 1367, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Garrison Development Corp. (Box 1367, Folder 2-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Garrison Development Corp. - Financial Statements (Box 1368, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Garrison Development Corp. - Financial - Loan Guaranty (Box 1368, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts (Box 1368, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations (Box 1369, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations - A-Z (Box 1369, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations to Speak - A-M (Box 1369, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations to Speak - B-N (Box 1370, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations to Speak - N-S (Box 1371, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations to Speak - S-Z (Box 1372, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Jewelry (Box 1372, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Mail (Box 1372, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Letterbook (Box 1372, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments (Box 1373, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Legal (Box 1373, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Loans (Box 1373, Folder 3-6, Box 1374, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Operation (Box 1374, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Photographs (Box 1375, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Politics (Box 1375, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property (Box 1375, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Hawaii (Box 1375, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Personal (Box 1376, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Procedures committee (Box 1376, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York - 834 Fifth Ave. (Box 1376, Folder 3-5, Box 1377, Folder 1-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Theodore Muller - Interior Decorator - LSR's Homes, 1966-1974 (Box 1378, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York - 235-41 East 46th St. Corp. (Box 1378, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York - Fishers Island (Box 1378, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - General (Box 1378, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - A-Z (Box 1379, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - A-M (Box 1379, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - N-Z (Box 1380, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Accounts (Box 1380, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Accounting - General, 1961-1965 (Box 1380, Folder 3-5, Box 1381, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Album (Box 1381, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Appraisals (Box 1381, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Boats (Box 1382, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Budget (Box 1382, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Construction, 1961-1964 (Box 1382, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Equipment Purchases and Requests (Box 1382, Folder 6-7)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Automobiles (Box 1383, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Fees (Gratuities at Ranch) (Box 1383, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Fish and Fishing (Box 1383, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Furnishings (Box 1383, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Grazing Lands (Rental of) (Box 1383, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Horse Purchase (Box 1384, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Insect Control (Box 1384, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Mathews, Red and Belle General Correspondence (Box 1384, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Memos (Box 1384, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Blueprints & Maps (Box 1385, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Lease (Box 1384, Folder 5-6, Box 1385, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Sale/Gift (Box 1385, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Transfer of Land (Box 1385, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - New Cabin (Box 1385, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - New Cabin - Prints - Plans (Box 1385, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Photographs (Box 1385, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 1385, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General Procedure (Box 1386, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General - A-Z (Box 1386, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General Correspondence (Box 1386, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1967-1976 (Box 1386, Folder 4-8, Box 1387, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 1388, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kent House and Grounds (Box 1388, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Rockwood Hall (Box 1388, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Rockwood Hall - General Correspondence (Box 1389, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Rockwood Hall - A-Z (Box 1389, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Rockwood Hall - Clippings (Box 1389, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Rockwood Hall - International Business Machines Corp. (IBM) (Box 1389, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock (Box 1390, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - A-L (Box 1390, Folder 2-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - M-Z (Box 1391, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Housing (Box 1391, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Alloway House (Box 1392, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Hollis Gale Property (Box 1392, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Industrial Site - Park (Box 1392, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson Visit, 1967 June 10-12 (Box 1392, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Legal (Box 1392, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 1392, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 1392, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation, Inc. (Box 1392, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Grants (Box 1392, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1393, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 1393, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - A-Z (Box 1394, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Barton Reports (Box 1394, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Clippings (Box 1395, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Finances (Box 1395, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Low Income Housing (Box 1395, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Opening (Box 1396, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 1408, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills - General Correspondence and Memos (Box 1396, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Radio/TV (Box 1396, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Real Estate - Larsen, Leslie H. (Box 1396, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Real Estate - 30 Rockefeller Plaza Associates & Co., 1959-1964 (Box 1397, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Real Estate - F.C. Feise Company (Box 1397, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Staff meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 1397, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips, 1948-1963 (Box 1398, Folder 1-7, Box 1399, Folder 1, Box 1397, Folder 4-10)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - South America, 1966 March-April (Box 1399, Folder 2-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips, 1962-1975 (Box 1400, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - South Pacific, 1972 (Box 1400, Folder 2-4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - South Pacific - Printed Material, 1972 (Box 1401, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - Alaska (Box 1401, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - Hawaii, Eastern Airlines, 1968 (Box 1647, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Selective Service - Naval Reserve, 1942-1947 (Box 1401, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art A-F (Box 1401, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art - A-P (Box 1405, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art - N-Z (Box 1406, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art - Printed Material (Box 1406, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art - Soldwedel, Frederic (Box 1406, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art - "Beaver Dick" Leigh (Box 1407, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Trusts (Box 1402, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trusts for Children (Box 1402, Folder 3-4, Box 1403, Folder 1-3, Box 1404, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Laura's Wedding (Box 1404, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Mark F. (Box 1404, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Meile (Box 1404, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Michael (Box 1404, Folder 6)
    Restricted - Michael Rockefeller
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance S., Mary French (Box 1407, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance S., Mary French - Addresses (Box 1407, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance S., Mary French - Property (Box 1407, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance S., Mary French - Billings Farm, Inc. (Box 1408, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance S., Mary French - Thoughts and Meditations (Box 1408, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Margaret D. (Peggy) (Box 1408, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 1408, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A-E (Box 1409, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - F-L (Box 1410, Folder 1-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - M-R (Box 1411, Folder 1-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - S-Z (Box 1412, Folder 1-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Addresses - A-F (Box 1412, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Addresses - G-Z (Box 1413, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Addresses - International European Movement (Box 1413, Folder 3, Box 1414, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Articles (Box 1414, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Articles - A-Z (Box 1414, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Autographs (Box 1415, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Automobiles (Box 1415, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Awards (Box 1415, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Biography (Box 1415, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Birthday, 1974 (Box 1416, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Birthday, 1975 (Box 1416, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Birthday, 1976 (Box 1416, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Boats (Box 1416, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Boats - North Sea Trawler (Box 1417, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Books (Box 1417, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 1417, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts 1976 (Box 1417, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Acknowledgments 1976 (Box 1417, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Received 1976 (Box 1417, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card 1975 (Box 1417, Folder 7, Box 1418, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card 1975 - A-Z (Box 1418, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - Miscellaneous List (Box 1418, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - IBEC (Box 1418, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - Museum of Modern Art (Box 1418, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - New York State (Box 1418, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - Office (Box 1418, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - Personal (Box 1418, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - United States Government (Box 1418, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1975 - Venezuela (Box 1419, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts 1975 (Box 1419, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Acknowledgement 1975 (Box 1419, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Received 1975 (Box 1419, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card 1974 (Box 1419, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 (Box 1419, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - Miscellaneous List (Box 1419, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - IBEC (Box 1419, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - New York State (Box 1419, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - Office (Box 1419, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - Personal (Box 1419, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - United States Government (Box 1419, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1974 - Venezuela (Box 1420, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts 1974 (Box 1420, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Acknowledgment 1974 (Box 1420, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Received 1974 (Box 1420, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card 1973 (Box 1420, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - Congressional (Box 1420, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - Executive Chamber and 55th St. (Box 1420, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - Governor's Club (Box 1420, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - Museum of Modern Art and Museum of Primitive Art (Box 1420, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - New York Legislature (Box 1420, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - Office (Box 1420, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1973 - Personal (Box 1421, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts 1973 (Box 1421, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts 1973 - Acknowledgment (Box 1421, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gifts Received 1973 (Box 1421, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - General Correspondence (Box 1421, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - Executive Chamber - 55th St. (Box 1421, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - Governor's Club (Box 1422, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - IBEC - Overseas & USA (Box 1422, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - Museum of Modern Art and Museum of Primitive Art (Box 1422, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - NARFARMS (Box 1422, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - New York State Delegation, County Chair and County Vice-Chair (Box 1422, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - New York State Legislature (Box 1422, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - Office (Box 1422, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - Personal (Box 1422, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Card List 1972 - Rockefeller Center and Music Hall (Box 1422, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas Gift List 1972 (Box 1422, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Christmas 1972 - Gifts Received (Box 1423, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons (Box 1423, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons - Echeverria Alvare, Luis, 1972 June 17 (Box 1423, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons - State Dinner at Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1973 May 11 (Box 1423, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons - Rainbow Room Lists, 1973 May 10 (Box 1424, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons - Republican Governors Association Luncheon, 1973 May 11 (Box 1424, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons (Box 1424, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dinners/Luncheons - Kissinger, Mr. and Mrs. Henry (Box 1424, Folder 4-6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Dyslexia (Box 1425, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Films (Box 1425, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Finances (Box 1425, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Finances - Investments (Box 1425, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Furnishings (Box 1425, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Gifts (Box 1425, Folder 6, Box 1426, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Gifts - Steuben Glass (Box 1426, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Giving Program (Box 1426, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Hauser (Box 1426, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations - A-B (Box 1426, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations - C-S (Box 1427, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations - T-Z (Box 1428, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations to Speak - A-C (Box 1428, Folder 2-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations to Speak - C-K (Box 1429, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations to Speak - L-P (Box 1430, Folder 1-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations to Speak - Q-Z (Box 1431, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Jewelry (Box 1432, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box 1432, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Memos (Box 1432, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Monthly Calendars (Box 1432, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Photos - A-D (Box 1432, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Photos - E-Z (Box 1433, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Printed Material (Box 1433, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property (Box 1433, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS (Box 1433, Folder 5-6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Finances (Box 1434, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Hacienda Palo Gordo (Box 1434, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Hacienda Palo Gordo - Reports (Box 1434, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Invega, Inc. (Box 1434, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Malnar, Inc. (Box 1434, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Malnar, Inc. - Dissolution (Box 1435, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro (Box 1435, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Baker (Box 1435, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Efferson (Box 1435, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Finances/Budget (Box 1435, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Inlaca (Box 1435, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1436, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Kimball, Edward (Box 1436, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Printed Material (Box 1436, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Reports (Box 1436, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Memos (Box 1436, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit (Box 1437, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 1437, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Lodge (Box 1437, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - New York City, 1930 (Box 1437, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 1438, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Washington - 2500 Foxhall Road (Box 1438, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Washington - 2500 Foxhall Road - Sale (Box 1438, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Radio/Television (Box 1439, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Radio/Television - NBC -"Meet the Press" - Appreciation (Box 1439, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Radio/Television - NBC -"Meet the Press" - Critical letters (Box 1439, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Rodgers, William H. (Box 1439, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Staff (Box 1439, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips (Box 1439, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - Southwestern United States, 1972 (Box 1439, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - Europe, 1973 March (Box 1440, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - Europe, 1973 July (Box 1440, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - Venezuela, 1974 May (Box 1440, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - Europe, 1975 June-July (Box 1440, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - World Trip, 1976 March-April (Box 1440, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - U.S. Government - Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs (Box 1440, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Wedding, 1963 (Box 1440, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Wines (Box 1440, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 1441, Folder 1-4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - Fundacao Ricardo Do Espirito Santo Silva (Box 1442, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - Contributions (Box 1442, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - Printed Material (Box 1442, Folder 3-4)